killertracks.com 2016-01-06

# Privacy Policy

_**PRIVACY POLICY**  
_

This notice discloses the online data collection and use practices of Killer Tracks (or “we”), 2110 Colorado Avenue, Suite 110, Santa Monica, CA 90404. Killer Tracks may modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time. We will indicate any changes by updating the date at the top of the policy. “the Website” means KillerTracks.com. "User" means you, the Website end-user. We encourage you to review this policy from time to time. You will signify your acceptance of this privacy policy when you request download access to the Website or take a license of rights to use our production music. Your continued usage of the Website or your continued licensing of our production music following the posting of any changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes. 

**1\. PRIVACY PRACTICES AND POLICIES & OUR USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Your e-mail address and other personally identifying data will be known to KILLER TRACKS only when you voluntarily submit such information to the Website. We may use this personal information to contact you if we change our services or terms or if we need to give you notice under those terms. 

The information about your licensing of our production music may be used to send you information that we believe may be of interest to you, such as information about music or products or services offered by KILLER TRACKS or its affiliates. 

If you decide at any time in the future that you wish to begin receiving such information (if you previously opted-out) or that you wish to cease receiving such information (if you previously opted-in), you may change your preferences at any time by changing your status in the “My Account” pages on the Website. The marketing messages (e-mails) that we send from info@killertracks.com will also always have an ‘unsubscribe’ option at the bottom of the message. 

**2\. WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**  
As a general rule, we will not disclose any personal information we collect from you without your consent. However, we may disclose personal information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. We may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

If you have opted-in to receive marketing information from us, we may share your information with our affiliated companies. We will not share your personal information with other third parties for marketing purposes without your consent. 

We may share with others, at our discretion, certain aggregate statistical data about licensing and the use of our production music. No personal information (such as names or email addresses) will be identifiable from such statistics. 

We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described above, including personally identifiable information, to third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of KILLER TRACKS. 

**3\. SECURITY**  
KILLER TRACKS strictly protects the security of your personal information and your choices for its intended use. We use current industry standard technology to maintain the confidentiality and accuracy of the information you provide to us. To protect your personal information, we use “secure servers” with industry standard SSL 128 bit key encryption. However, we cannot guarantee that any information you submit to us will be free from unauthorized third party intrusion. 

**4\. CHANGE/MODIFY**  
If at any point you no longer wish to receive communications from KILLER TRACKS, please forward such requests to us at the relevant office address which is found on the contacts page. 

**5\. COOKIES**  
The Website has features that automatically collect information from users to assist us in recognizing our users’ preferences and serving their needs. The Website uses cookies, which are small data files containing information about the user that are stored on the user’s hard drive. Some cookies are used to make login to the Website easier (such as by remembering usernames and passwords). If users reject cookies, they may be limited in using some areas of the Website. Cookies can also enable us to track users’ movements and target their interests to enhance their experience on the Website. We may also collect clickstream data and assign unique identifiers to our users for the same purpose. Information obtained with these technologies may be associated with personal information for registered users. 

We or a third-party advertisement server may also use cookies in connection with targeting advertisements or promotions to users. Our advertisers and other third parties whose products or services are promoted on our sites may also use cookies or other technology, and we advise you to check their privacy policies for information about their cookies and other privacy practices. 

For our internal purposes, we may gather information such as the date, time, browser type, navigation history, and IP address of all visitors to our site(s). We use this information for our internal security audit log, trend analysis, and system administration, and to gather broad demographic information about our user base for aggregate use.

[Click here to view the Killer Tracks website Terms & Conditions.](http://www.killertracks.com/#/Privacy%20Terms/terms-conditions.aspx)
